<resources>
    <!-- Strings for buttons -->
    <string name="buildafrankButtonText">BUILD YOUR OWN FRANK</string>
    <string name="reserveTableButtonText">RESERVE A TABLE</string>
    <string name="contactButtonText">CONTACT US</string>
    <string name="menuButtonText">MENU</string>
    <string name="billEstimatorText">BILL ESTIMATOR</string>
    <string name="emailButtonText">Email Us</string>
    <string name="addToContactButtonText">ADD TO CONTACTS</string>
    <string name="findLocationButtonText">FIND LOCATION</string>
    <string name="goToWebsiteButtonText">GO TO WEBSITE</string>
    <string name="shareButtonText">SHARE WITH A FRIEND</string>
    <string name="bookTableButton">Book Table</string>
    <string name="estimate_bill_button">Estimate your Bill</string>

    <string name="app_name">Frank \'N\' Steins</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open" translatable="false">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close" translatable="false">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment" translatable="false">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <!-- Additional Text Strings -->
    <string name="mainDescriptionText">Welcome to Frank \'N\' Steins: a place where Frankers and Frankettes of all ages can come and enjoy some of the most delicious, one-of-a-kind Franks you\'ll ever taste!</string>
    <string name="mainDescriptionText2">We also host some of the finest Steins on tap as well as many delicious beers on bottle for our 19+ patrons.</string>
    <string name="mainscreenFeaturesText">Please enjoy our app. With it, you can check out our menu, get in contact with us, make a table reservation, get an estimation on your bill and even build your own custom Frank! Check out some of app features below:</string>
    <string name="mainSubtitleText">Gourmet Franks\nand\nTasty Steins!</string>
    <string name="contactTitleText">Contact Us!</string>
    <string name="contactInfoText">Frank \'N\' Steins Restaurant\\n1178 Tecumseh Road W, Windsor\\n(519) - 780 3445\\nfranknsteins@gmail.com\\nwww.franknsteins.ca</string>
    <string name="additionalInfoText">Additional contact features:</string>
    <string name="tableReserveIntroText">Select a date, time, and hit the \'Book Table\' button to book your table!</string>

    <!-- Frank Menu Strings -->
    <string name="classicfrank_desc">The deliciously tried and true Frank with traditional
                toppings like ketchup, mustard, and relish.</string>
    <string name="breakfastfrank_desc">The early bird gets the Frank with this morning time
                special. This frank comes with an egg cooked just how
                you like it topped with bacon and hash browns. For those
                of you with a sweet tooth, try it with delicious maple
                syrup.</string>
    <string name="frankophone_desc">The spirit of French Canada is alive and well with this Canadian
                classic. The Frankophone combines the greatness of the Frank
                with the patriotic dish known as poutine. This Frank is topped
                with gravy and cheese curds imported from Quebec.</string>
    <string name="pizzafrank_desc">Can\’t decide between Pizza or Franks tonight? Try a Pizza Frank topped
                with mozzarella cheese, pizza sauce, pepperoni, and mushrooms.</string>
    <string name="franksgiving_desc">Remind everyone what you’re thankful for this year with this festive
                Frank topped with gravy, corn, and creamy mashed potatoes.</string>
    <string name="frankzilla_desc">Think you can handle the sheer size and fire of the legendary Frankzilla?
                This Frank is three times the size of a regular Frank and comes topped
                with our secret Frank \'N\' Steins Hot Sauce, jalapeno peppers, and is
                lightly spiced with ghost pepper powder. Frankzilla will leave its mark
                on you.</string>
    <string name="frankobandito_desc">Travel back to the Wild West with this cowboy-inspired Frank. This Frank comes
                topped with onion rings, tomatoes, and our zesty BBQ sauce that will make you
                feel like a modern-day buckaroo.</string>
    <string name="frankoitaliano_desc">A taste of Italy captured inside a juicy Frank! This Frank comes topped with
                provolone cheese, olives, olive oil, tomato, and lettuce.</string>
    <string name="deutschfrank_desc">A classic bratwurst (sausage) topped with mustard, sauerkraut, accompanied
                with a small potato salad. Experience the taste of Oktoberfest!</string>
    <string name="frankwallace_desc">A Frank with a Scottish twist. The Frank Wallace comes topped with a traditional
                Scottish haggis: a pudding-like topping of sheep\’s pluck, minced with onion,
                oatmeal, suet, spices, and salt. They can take your land, but they\'ll never take
                your Frank!</string>

    <!-- Frank Stein Strings -->
    <string name="frankweiser_desc">Our custom classic lager. Smooth and crisp, this Stein is the perfect companion
                to any Frank</string>
    <string name="fpa_desc">The Frank \'N\' Steins twist on the traditional India Pale Ale. This hoppy Stein will
                satiate even the savviest Stein drinker.e</string>
    <string name="frankwinterstein_desc">A holiday-themed Stein with a hint of chocolate to it. Warm your heart while
                this tasty Stein quenches your thirst.</string>
    <string name="steinomead_desc">Travel back to the days of Vikings and pillage your way through some delicious
                Franks with the assistance of our mead-beer blended Stein. Sweet and tangy
                like mead with the smooth crispiness of a beer.</string>
    <string name="frankinapint_desc">For the true Frank fanatic. This lager is flavored to taste exactly like our
                amazing Classic Frank. For a 100% Frank experience, go with this Stein.</string>
    <string name="steinsred_desc">This Belgian Red beer follows the tradition of slightly soured red ale. Steins Red goes
                great solo or accompanied by a tasty Frank.</string>
    <string name="frankporter_desc">The Frank ‘N’ Steins porter has been a staple brand at our restaurant. This dark Stein
                may seem mysterious, but it packs a ton of flavor.</string>
    <string name="steinslite_desc">A lighter Stein for those seeking an alternative Stein. All the flavor of the Classic
                Frank, but even smoother.</string>

    <!-- Frank Stein Strings -->
    <string name="pop">Pop</string>
    <string name="milk">Milk</string>
    <string name="choc_milk">Chocolate Milk</string>
    <string name="water">Water</string>
    <string name="icedtea">Iced Tea</string>
    <string name="lemonade">Lemonade</string>
    <string name="applejuice">Apple Juice</string>
    <string name="coffee">Coffee</string>
    <string name="alcoholfreeweiser">Alcohol Free Frankweiser</string>

    <!-- Bill estimator strings -->


    <!-- Strings related to Settings -->
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="pref_language_summary">Change the application language</string>
    <string name="pref_language_title">Language</string>
    <string-array name="pref_language">
        <item>English</item>
        <item>Français</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pref_language_values">
        <item>en</item>
        <item>fr</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="changed_lang">Language changed. Returning to main menu</string>



</resources>
